#### +61 451118592

hemanthkamalseva@gmail.co https://www.linkedin.com/in/itsshk/ https://github.com/SHK-develops

# **Junior Developer**

# **Summary**



1.5 years of experience developer responsible for maintaining, testing, and developing various websites and mobile applications using multiple tools and technologies. I got a proficient knowledge of programming languages like HTML, CSS, Dart, Python, PHP, C, C++, Firebase, and MySQL Databases.

# **Work Experience**



### Junior Web Developer | Vertebral Pty Ltd

Nov 2021 - Present (1 year 4 months)

Development and maintenance of the host company's website and CRM Solution.

- Created schema code for the existing website's rating, location, services, and product search.
- Tested and documented Local Gym CRM Software.
- Management of mobile application development.



### Junior Developer | Outback Ventures Pty Ltd

Jun 2020 - Oct 2021 (1 year 5 months)

Development of websites using PHP and cross-platform mobile applications using Flutter and Firebase Technologies.

- UI application development using HTML and CSS.
- Developed mobile application prototype.
- Tested and documented developed application.



### **Project Leader | Federation University Australia**

April 2020- Jul 2020 (4 months)

Development of messaging application (iOS & Android) with industry founder using Flutter and Firebase Technologies.



#### **Tutor | Vygo**

Apr 2019 - Jul 2020 (1 year 4 months)

Vygo works as a mobile platform that helps university students improve grades with better access to affordable peer tutors, whilst also giving students a 'business in a box' to earn money on campus, tutoring classes they have recently aced.



#### Mentor | Coder Dojo

Jul 2019 - Aug 2019 (2 months)

Teaching and mentoring school-going kids how to design and develop games by using codes blocks in Scratch.

# **Skills**



Agile Methodology, Dart language, Teamwork, PHP Programming, HTML, CSS, Web Application Development, UI, Testing, Java Programming, Firebase, MySQL, Team Building, GitHub, Atlassian Jira, Dart Programming, Figma, Python Programming, Lisp Programming Language, C++ Programming, Microsoft Products

# **Education History**



Masters (Software Engineering) | Federation University Australia

Class of 2020 GPA 6.0



Bachelors (Electronic and Communication) | JNTUK Andhra Pradesh India

Class of 2017 GPA 4.5

## **Certifications**



Advanced Google Analytics | Google

Aug 2021 - Aug 2024



Data Visualization using Power BI | Great Learning

Sep 2021 - Current



**Cloud Application Developer | Salesforce** 

Feb 2021 - Current



Foundations of Front-End Web Development | Udemy

May 2019 - Current

### References



Yasien (Employer) | Vertebral Pty Ltd

+61 405 140 333

info@vertebral.com.au



Praveen (Employer) | Outback Ventures Pty Ltd

+61 433 385 799

info@outbakventures.com